Something I've noticed in the UK is that
we have a very strange attitude towards
what is lunch, especially when it's like
an event or a public occasion. Like,
have you ever been to an event that
started at 12:00 or 1:00 in the middle
of the day and they provided [music]
like snacks or nibbles? And you're
thinking it's lunchtime. I need a proper
meal. We really put so much more [music]
emphasis on dinner being the proper meal
and at lunch people seem to just get by
on not much food. I don't know how they
do it, honestly. Like a bit of bread or
crisps with dip, sausage rolls, or maybe
soup if you're lucky. I know that people
I've met from other complain about this.
Like, why do I go to this work event and
you think that food should be provided
given the time of day that the event is
at, but actually you're just left
[music] kind of fending for yourself and
feeling hungry. And a lot of the time
you have to stand and eat. You can't
[music] even sit down. This is something
we do really badly in our culture, I
have to say. Food needs to come first,
people. Make it healthy, make it hot,
make it substantial enough that people
feel full. Just putting that out there,
that's my opinion. Have you had this
experience? What do you think?